A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of Civilian Defense, 1940-1945.
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Correspondence with localities, 1942-1945., Extent: XX cubic feet (XX boxes). (Box XX)
  - Correspondence with locatilities, 1943-1945.
    - Gloucester County
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Goochland County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Grayson County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Greene County
      - General, 1943. (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Greensville County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Halifax County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilizaiton, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Hanover County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Harrisonburg-Rockingham County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - General - Identification cards, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - General - Negro activities, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - General - Publications, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - General - Publicity, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - General - Service awards, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization - V-Home Campaign, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Henrico County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Henrico County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Highland County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Hopewell, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Block plan, 1943. (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Isle of Wight County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - James City County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - King George County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - King and Queen County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - King William County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Lancaster County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Lee County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Lexington, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Moblization, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Loudoun County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Louisa County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Lunenburg County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Luray, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Lynchburg, City of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - General - Compensation, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - General - Conferences and meetings, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - General - Negro Civilian Defense activities, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - General - Publicity, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - General - Reports, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - General - Transportation, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Car Sharing, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food Preservation, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Junior Citizens Service Corps, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Volunteer Office, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Civilian Protection - Air Raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Protection - Masks and pennants, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Protection - Training films, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Protection - Responsibilities list, 1943. (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Madison County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Martinsville, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Mathews County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Mecklenburg County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Middlesex County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Millboro, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Nansemond County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Nelson County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - New Kent County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Newport News, City of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - General - Conferences and meetings, 1943. (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - General - Identification cards, 1943. (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - General - Publications, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - General - Publicity, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Block plan, 1943-1944. (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Car Sharing, 1943. (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Conservation of critical resources, 1944. (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Housing, 1944. (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Nutrition, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Salvage, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Victory Gardens, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Protection - Evacuation authority, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection - Masks and pennants, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection - Plant protection and responsibility list, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection - Training schools, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk, City of
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - General - Priorities, 1943. (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - General - Publications, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - General - Publicity, 1943-1944. (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - General - Service awards, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Conferences, 1943. (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Conservation of critical resources, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Food preservation, 1943. (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Health, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Nutrition, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943-1945. (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Victory Gardens, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Volunteer Office, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943 Sep-Dec. (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943 Jun-Aug. (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943 Apr-May. (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943 Jan-Mar. (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection - Plant protection and responsibility list, 1943-1944. (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Protection - Training schools, 1943. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943-1945. (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - North Tazewell, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943. (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Northampton County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Northumberland County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Moblization, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Nottoway County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Orange County
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1945. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Page County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943. (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Pamplin, Town of
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Patrick County
      - General, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Petersburg
      - General, 1943-1945. (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - General - Insignia, 1943. (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - General - Publications, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Civilian Mobilization, 1943-1945. (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Child care, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Conserve Critical Resources, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Office of Price Administration, 1943-1945. (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Civilian Mobilization - The Petersburg Defender (newsletter), 1943-1945. (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Civilian Mobilization - Salvage, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Civilian Protection, 1943-1944. (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Civilian Protection - Air raid precautions, 1943-1945. (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Civilian Protection - Federal equipment, 1943-1945. (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Civilian Protection - Masks and pennants, 1943. (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Civilian Protection - Training schools, 1943. (Box 82, Folder 3)